First the pandemic. Then the chaos.
Alone is a horror, thriller film directed by Johnny Martin.
When an outbreak hits, Aidan barricades himself inside
his apartment and starts rationing food.
His complex is overrun by infected Screamers, and with the world falling apart
into chaos, he is left completely alone fighting for his life.
Aidan, played by Tyler Posey.
Eva, played by Summer Spiro.
Edward, played by Donald Sutherland.
Brandon, played by Robert Ri'chard.
Jessica, played by Brooke Swallow.
Jack Brian, played by Eric Etebari.
Alone (released in the UK as Final Days) is a 2020 American horror film directed
by Johnny Martin and starring Tyler Posey and Donald Sutherland.
The film follows a young man who barricades himself inside
his apartment during a zombie apocalypse.
The film was released on October 16, 2020.
The film explores themes of invasion, zombie, pandemic, horror, thriller.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking and intense.